Wertheimer, Barbara Additional Files 5736
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Barbara Wertheimer Additional Files
1820-1987
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wertheimer, Barbara
5736
26 cubic feet
25 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Professor Wertheimer's office file focused largely on women in the workforce. Includes files on trade union women studies, the Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, and the Coalition of Trade Union Women (CLEW).
3123618
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 24, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Barbara Mayer Wertheimer (1926-September 23, 1983) was an American labor historian and labor organizer from the 1940s through the early 1980s.
From 1947 to 1948 Ms. Wertheimer was an organizer and acting education director for the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. She worked briefly for the American Labor Education Service and then from 1961 to 1966 as a consultant for the New York State Division of Housing and Community Renewal. In 1966 Ms. Wertheimer joined the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University. While at Cornell she was a senior extension associate, director of the Trade Union Women's Studies program, and, from 1977 on, an associate professor and director of the Institute for Women and Work, which she cofounded. Ms. Wertheimer remained at Cornell until her death in 1983.
Ms. Wertheimer is well known for her monograph "We Were There: The Story of Working Women in America" (1977).
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4015: Barbara Wertheimer Office Files 5729: Barbara Wertheimer Research Files 5736 P: Barbara Wertheimer Photographs 6144: Barbara Wertheimer Additional Files 6144 AV: Barbara Wertheimer Collection of Audio Recordings
Wertheimer, Barbara M.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3123618
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Working Women's Program for Research and Education, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Task Force - Tr. Union Women (UCLEA), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Cab. Studies April 18, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Working Women's Program for Research and Education, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- TMW Applications, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Applicants Minority Women Labor Education, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Minority + Proposal, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Report 2 Muskiwinni, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Musikiwinni Report #1, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Term 3 - TMW, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Term 3 - TMW, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Interview Schedule TMW, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- TMW - Year 2, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Muskiwinni Reapplication March 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Session 2, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Section 3, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Section 4, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Session 5, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Course Materials FinlabHist, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Slide Show, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Session 8 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Session 9 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Section 10, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- 12 Week Labor History Outline, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Material - Women w/ Labor History, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Minority Women, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- March 16 - Lab Ed 2, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Women in Labor Hist. Course Notes - May '74 Mitchell King, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Local 342, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Community Interviews Local 342, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Local 342, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Labor Ed. Spring 1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Labor Ed. - Spring 1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- UAW - NY, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- 1977 Summer School Notes (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Flight Attendants, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Flight Attendants - Prelim. Proposal, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Pre-Ret. Project, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Mimi, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- State-Wide Network, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Network File, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Network Proposal - Carnegie - Sept. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- School of the Sky/ + Other Proposal Ideas, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- August 17- Susan, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- FF Proposal, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Ford Grant 1975-77, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Ford Grant 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- FG (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Ford Grant - P.R., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Refunding - 1975-77, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Study Grant - Barriers to Partic. (Ford), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Working Women's Program for Research and Education, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Working Women's Program for Research and Education, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Trade Union Women's Studies, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Outlines, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Completed- Originals - Re-Typed, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Wire, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Institute - May 13/77, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- May 13, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Institute, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Rockefeller Study, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Rockefeller Grant, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Ford Re-Application., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Banking, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Carnegie - 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Grant - Carnegie, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Institute. Proposal - ILR Fac. 1976 (Passed 5/13/77), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- FF - Description, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- FF Proposal - 10/15/71, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Chase - P.R., 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Chase, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Budget 77-79 FF, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Ford Report June '75- Nov. '76, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lori Goldstock - Ithaca (C. Cook) (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Meeting Notes, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- For Report to R.D. Women's Programs, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- "Working with People" 7/13/77, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Task Force Responses, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Final Proposal - Fipse, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Summer/School 1981 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Summer Schools - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- 1982 Summer School (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Summer School 1978 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Rutgers Summer School 1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Summer School 1979 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- June 1, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Session 1, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Working women's Program for Research and Education (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Workshop Manuals, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Misc., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Mid-Career- 2nd Career, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- DC37 - TUWS, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- 1977 Summer School - Penn State (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Peer Counseling, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Summer School (Eval.) 1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- The University of Connecticut, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Summer School 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Local 342, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Women's Group - Working Women, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- 342 Ex. Bd. Program+ UA, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- District 65, 1964-1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- IAM - Lodge 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Teacher Training Conference March 29-30, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Ana Proposal, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Human Rights Hearing 4.21.75, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- NYC - Women's Advisers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Evaluation of First National Conference on Research, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Indus. Gerontology, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- NUEA, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Steingut - Panel, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Summer Institute 1976 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- P.R. Committee, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- P.R. Comm. Notes, Spring 1982 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Albany NCW Reg. MT April 1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- April 26-27 - Harvard Conference, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Source + Background For Grant - St. B.C., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Oral History, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Trade Union Women's Studies, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Trade Union Women's Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Women and International (Originals), 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Women and International World of Work - Proceedings, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Women, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Women's Studies, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Proceeding - International World of Work May 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- May 2 Conference Women and International World of Work, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Proceedings DS, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Dec 4, 5, 6 Conference Blue Collar Working woman, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Proceedings Focus on Women Unionists, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Focus on Women's Unionists, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Nov. 14, 1974 "Focus on Women Unionists (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Nov. 14, 1974 "Focus on Women Unionists" (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Nov. 14, 1974 Conference (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Trade Union Women's Studies, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Trade Union Women's Studies, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- January 19, 1974 Conference (Box 6, Folder 18)
- First N.Y. Trade Union Women's Conference Jan. 19, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Trade Union Women's Studies, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum Sophie Melvin- Gerson and the Gastonia, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated. Meat cutters Local 342 Conference 4/21-23/72, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Women's Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Correspondence African Project '78, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Expense African Project April - June 1978 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Women - Mgt. - Rights List, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Early Retirement, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Oral History U of M 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- For June 7 - Albany SUNY - Women's Studies, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Work in America Institute, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- AAA, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Followups, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Trade Union Women's Studies, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Trade Union Women's Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Planning Mt. 1982 School 11/19-20/81, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- National Conf. of Labor Union Women (Box 7, Folder 12)
- New School Course Woman Power - Fall 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- U.S. Course - Outline + Session 1 Notes, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- April 18 - NCNW, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- June + July Article, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Minor. Comm. - Ithaca, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Board Report 6/30/81, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Betty Lall - Proposal Draft, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Current Grant Ideas, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Grants, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Tap Pilot Prog. Ideas, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- ACTP - Cornell Project Proposal, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Texas (Austin) Nov. 9.-11, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Steering Comm. - 1982 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Retiree Grant Prog., 1974 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Union Admin. GJ (Box 7, Folder 27)
- ACTWU Proposal, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Ed. Outreach Front, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Proposal Ideas on Hold, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Cefres Conf. Jan 22-25/79, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Mar. 26, 1979 - AJC Conf. The Family, The City, Muti-Ethnics (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Women's Workforce Conf. '79, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- P.L. Board No. 3604 Southern Pacific- BLE Vol. II, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- New York State School of Industrial Labor Relations, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- ILR Letters, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- ILR Letters, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- ILR Letters, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- ILR Letters, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- ILR Letters, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Labor Ed. Correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- CWA Correspondence on Conference Proposal/Budget, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Misc. (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Request for Materials (Box 8, Folder 11)
- 5716 Box 8, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- New Zealand, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Leave Request, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- W.B. Project - K. Clarenbach, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Annual Report 1973-74, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Personal, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Memos - TUWS, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Labor Inst. For Human Enrichment, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Memos - Ithaca - FF, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Offices Memos Carol U. Etc., 1974 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Board Mt. 6/30/81, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 1982-83 Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Homer - Budget (2-82), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Budget, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Institute Board, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Research Ideas, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Commissioners State Wide Advisory Council, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Nov. 19 - Buffalo, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Alice Cook, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Albion college March 20-22, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Extension Planning Comm., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Programs April 1971- April 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Program Plans 1972-73, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Praeger, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Article: Search For Partnership 7/15/74, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Comm. On Employment, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Articles Speeches July, October, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- LLA - L.I. 1972 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Brooklyn. Mus. April 17, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- National Commission on Women + Work - (NIE Background), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Labor Advis. Mt. (Follow Up) Met. Dist., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Current Memos June 1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Cornell Credit for TUWS, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Annual Report 1981-82, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- 1982-83 Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- 1981-82 Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Annual Report 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Directives, 1973-1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- 1980-81 Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Staff Memos, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Oct. 24 Merle et al., 1975 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Budget Meetings Mar. 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- May 10-11 Training Session, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- 1979-80 #3, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- 1979-1980 (#2) (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Longitudinal Analysis of students, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Formal Listing of Students 74-75, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- TUWS F-UP Data 1974-5 Class, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Student Self-Evaluations 9/76, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Final Self-Eval 1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- 1976-77 TUWS Roster, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Entering Students 6/77, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- All info Sept. 1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Rosters, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Allrough Academic Records/Grades 74-75, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Public Info., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Social Security Numbers, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Public Info., 1973 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Interviewers and Women Interviewed, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- DC. 37 Longitudinal Report 1977 (Data) (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Union Representation, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Long T. Study, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Updates Hollow, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Actual Interviews Longitunials, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Appendices, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Sample Forms to Include, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Case Examples Longitudinal Report, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Longit. Survey, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- For Final FF Report, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Teachers Evaluation, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Updates Blue, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Longitudinal Report of Trade Union Women's Studies, 1974-1977 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Reading Lists Retired Workers, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- NYC Dept. for the Aging Retired Workers School, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Course Description Retired Workers School Cornell, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Source Materials Retired Workers School, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Useful Statistics on Sessions, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Inter - Longshoreman's Association, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Newspaper Guild Retirees, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Retirees Assn. DC37, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Retirees Local United Storeworkers Mary Leyden, Ret. Pres., 1975 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Advisory Prospects Retired Workers School, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Bulletins on Refined Persons Unions + Agencies, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Citizens Committee on Aging, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Foundation Prospects Retired Workers School, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Evaluations Self + Program, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- 1975-76 Finances of Students, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Finances 1974 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Complete Longitudinal, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Listings Info 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Reporting on Extension Programs (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Program Plans BW, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Requests for Syracuse Proceedings, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Annual Report 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - BW July-Sept. '75, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Correspondence -BW Oct. -Dec. '75, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - BW Jan. Mar. '76, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Correspondence - BW Oct. -Dec. '76, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Correspondence - BW July - Sept. '76, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Correspondence - BW April - June '76, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Interoffice Memos - BW, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Ford Foundation, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Project Information, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Press Releases, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Suppl. Q., 1973 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Xerox of Mats to Lenny, etc., 1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Ann Nelson, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Anne Nelson - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Barbara Wertheimer, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Ford Foundation, 1973-1977 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Speaking Engagements 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- TR.UN - Women's conf., 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Settlement Housing Fund, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Trade Union Women's Studies, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Dec. 5-6, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Blue Collar Conf., 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Blue Collar Conf. T, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Child Care (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Dec. 4,5,6 - 1974 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Labor Prog. Staff Mts., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Fall '73 Queens, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Buffalo ILR Women's Conf. Notes June 1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- AA Conf. Idea, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Summer 1975 Interview- Film (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Oct. 1, 1977 - New School Women + Money (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Austin, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Nat'l Council Negro Women, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- NEH - My Metro, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Vietnam, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Conf. on Aging CBJA - April 2, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Conf. Chaos or Security Aging - 1970's, 1970-1979 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Midwest Conference of Union Women Leaders, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Labor College, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- FF Interview Notes, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Book- Study Prager '72-'73, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Implications, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- FF - Agendas, Mts, Etc., 1972 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Local 342, 1973-1977 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Notes on 7 Unions, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Study of women in N.Y.C. Unions, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Management - Women, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Extensions Comm. 1975-77, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Extension Comm. 1975-77, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- NY Administrators (Pace), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- State-Wide Conf., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- UCLEA Newsletter, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- American Arbitration Association Conference,: Feb. 12, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Conf. 3/25 follow up, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- IAM Lodge 1987 - Survey, 1967-1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Local 1199 - Report Programs, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Pre-Ret. HB - Final Draft, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- TNT Conf. June 19-21, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Staff Program - Retirees, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Leadership Training, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Senior Center (Cultural), 1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- NYTU Women's Conf. and Follow up, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Pre-Ret. - 1199, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- 1199, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- 22, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- CU 3 Rough (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Local 1597, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- DC 37- 1597, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Dept. Store Union Local 2-3, Women (Michelson), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Store, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- FF - Interviewers, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Am Airlines TH. Attendants, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Barbara M. Wertheimer Director Working Women's Program for Research and Education and Trade Union Women's Studies NYSSILR-Cornell University, 1972- 1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- AAA/WWPRE Proceedings, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Police Foundation, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Provost's Advisory Comm. 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- African- Amer. Labor Center Prog., 1978 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Misc. (Box 16, Folder 16)
- CWA, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- CWA - May 30, 1978 Wash, DC Mt. (Box 16, Folder 18)
- UCLEA - Mar. 1978 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Local 463 - IUE, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- IUE-463, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- IUE, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Local 1199, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- 1199 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- File for Annual Rep. 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Prog. Plans - 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Women - FF Study Correspondence, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - AC, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Aug. 25/ ACWA St. Louis, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Sept. 14-15 - Ithaca 1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- New Approaches to Coll. Power - 4 working R's Orgs C. Seifer - Feb. 1977 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Comment, Paper - UCLEA Eastern Reg., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Search for Partnership Role, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- U of Michigan (notes) 11/17, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Article with N. Seifer, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Teacher Deval. Conf. 3/29-30/77, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Meeting Notes, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Nov. 16 Long Island 1977 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- S.E.D. Conf. May 18 Notes - see on Grant funding (Box 17, Folder 19)
- June 30/70 TUWS Staff Follow Up Mt., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Conf. and Meeting Notes, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Effective Letter Writing 75 Mosil, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Class 1 Union Administration, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Working Women and the Law 75M156L, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- NYC Comm. On Status of Women Leadership Training 75M155L, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- CWA Grievance Handling 75M135L (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Parliamentary Procedure 74M283L (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Working Women and the Law 75M28L, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Working Women: Problems 75M009L, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Spring '75, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Parliamentary Procedure, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Women and the Law, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Summary Fall '74, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Spring '74 Short course Evaluations, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Dist. 65 Speaking and Law 74M119L, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Public Speaking - Storeworkers 74M112L, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Effective Speaking 74M037L, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Effective Speaking (dana) 74M077L, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 17)